Gentleman we are here to do homage to one
who has filled the bottom of the cheek
with wonder who wrote to the top just
like I read this manifest faithfully
delivered our products achieving
a record for which we may all be justly
proud the are really Bible record four
hundred twenty eight points Mr Madison I
can see that. This really doesn't thank
you I'm sure and there are others
among you want just I think
a lot of them mention you Mr Ackerman for
your splendid record of three hundred
ninety seven points. But there are
no men who has been with us but
a short time one in that
short time ago came to
a wonderful record I congratulate
you Mr Snodgrass. And you Mr
Scott undeserving
a lot of the mention of
you and you you and. See
you later now or just
a moment at about the
pulse of our public. Now
in this area here we find.
Is this area here we find
that our sales are for
I say in this area ourselves are falling
far below what they should there is no way
to.
Please the US.
We find in this area here that our business
is falling off while the debacle that
is seems to be on the streets. As I would
say that in this area we find. In this
area I am telling you that we find our
shares are falling to the what they should
and we are losing on our customers now
something is wrong now the question is
what is wrong why I answered I ask you
there is no reason I can
see it now that was wrong.
But we what's the matter with you I guess
trying to make you know how that is so I
don't I never drinking sounds are going
to play tricks on you to give you that oh
don't give it to me so I'll probably
that's Clara's went to the he caught me in
that whole know how
you'll know that gave me.
The.
Harvest Moon checksums I'll say this already
gone. Only my way all I know I'll be
reading out in front I think it's terrible
that went now from me to yet barely.
Well I'll be there any time you said so I
wasn't me do don't worry obviously yes
I think we got
a stay at home he feels good because. You
know I'm legit so cause I was getting
tired. Yes I know you to.
Me You gave us the wrong hat the whole
this very funny if you tell me where they
explain I'll try and miss it. We
like you. We don't listen what happened
did you lose your address book yes yes
watch me that's what I
thought Good night what
a god. You give me my hat.
Give me my hat let's I've got
a great idea let's all go over to your
house does ever confuse that I might be
somebody's sister oh this. Listen
I'm warning you my brother is
a very tough man guy and Brian
Banks. That he's got it all right.
Well you sure are
a little mad say you
post can do this for you
a lot more brother how to leave Yeah
can you Jennifer. Serious seeing
somebody. Couldn't take math we're
going to tell you the same way
the CIA The CIA said. Daddy
put it on and on for
a year I'm not as I have no problem gangsters
should be arrested I've got to do my
duty as American citizen.
What's your name Joe
Monroe asked me again
you're STILL NO NO. Oh God
give us a chance to make
a dying statement this is simply brilliant
and dangerous All right this I know made
you know it when taking get
away with that decision she had
a puppet do that's who I am
and who are you that it.
Might be
a. Son I. Don't
want and I don't. Watch much. But
this guy in the middle I can't get out by
selling energy I'd like to shake the hand
of the man I'm not out to middleweight
champion editor Next I read Obama
middleweight champion knocked up by
a truck driver I read
all about extra. Well
I kind of got you know it's funny that Gabby
now every time of the sound something
happens that is it was
a real something happens and then you
eat oh I see why dynamite looking up
a forty one other can listen I want
to Nevada Utah and I said of those.
C.
. Speed. I
don't know I don't. Have
a space by. How do I get this mouse. I
was.
Of course you weren't you. What. Was it.
You shouldn't come in here when Gabby's
out of town he might think it was not on
the level he would notice that
anything that was morning Plato played
a lot let's keep it simple How
did you get that oh this is
I was shadow boxing about zero one
No it was like this spider came in
we started to sparring and I ran into one
when I went to what I call last night in
the shower tub more accidents
happen in bathrooms look
that's the story of the
Lion and the mouse it's
a lie and sue the paper. And. What did
say truck drive another chance all it must
be someone among some other middleweight
champion there right now was a little
way can not officially listen and be
a pal you're not going to say anything to
Gabby about this are you he reads just as
easy but he's in
Philadelphia the Ivy I got
a paper there now. Your
idea I think I'll give you a step at
a time and it better be ten minutes or
we'll write whatever you have it you're
going to want to meet follow your reputation
walk down the street and have the
whole town talking about you now well
twelve years ago and I don't I want to have
a ride What's that got to do with it nothing.
Except the still talking about it you
see that all that about it is. Not
a Remind me to ask you later what you were
doing in here with him I wish you cared
. Well.
You dumb cluck your thick skull you're
right I want to configure falling so much
I'm glad I'm going to save yourself I got
it got the needle you know middleweight
champion of the world.
Yesterday you had a talk with
a million dollars to date and with a
nickel I'm in Philly signing up to be
a good man of a twenty G.'s I got
a pen my all ready to sign I want to happen
yeah that's what I want to know oh wow
and you want to know what happened. They
want to know what happened who they want
to know what I was one of the boys I got
again the statement of your biggest story
ready we're going to head off Allison Well
I said I give you space for ten minutes
Well I always just by way I said ten
minutes tonight. Rach are coming up
five Come on come on come on listen Gabby
it was like this spider and I were
out walking down the street
and up comes a guy what
a guy right Debbie he was the biggest cry
of us all big bush he was big Didn't
Jenny it we. Were hands this biggest boredom
How did he wind his watch Speed look
like this alongside him I had to jump up
on to get ahead of my way to meet women
this is Chase
a big guy. Either way it knocked out
by heavy weight that's an angle that
a spider. Got it right why did I say
they Hello they'll take it up from there
hello. Who's the.
The truck drive above the Sullivan is on
his way up that's all hide under the bed
become everybody come. On the big sticks
on his way up he pointed it out Stan great
was going to picture the Julia you know
like YOU DON'T KNOW IT guy little guy. The
public is going to get you long for that
big brother why you didn't get sympathy
you don't because you know why I
say we can take that man mostly.
What you want I'm for the cell phone
itself hands as big as watermelons
going silent.
Hello there. No you know how I
got our economy going get the
press get the press I lay em out of sight
of the picture and only I'm going I'm
over here in the sunlight of the working
photograph the body the way even if way
that boy make any more mistakes and are you
sure that you're the man and not doubt
our Mr Big fall Yes ma'am or your pretty
little more you usually find it was going
to hold will get up enough stock talk the
first place you've got to cut out all
this rough stuff like us I spent I guess
on well we've all read the papers
we glance through them Robin is.
Very gaunt again shut up are come on
now I don't know how you folks feel about
all this but it's got me worried you're
looking well for thank you this thing was
partly my fault. All right to sit down
and. Now to just how it started
you see I'd never had my
name in the papers when I saw
a chance to get in the headlights. You
don't know what they did to me See I lead
a very simple life and all that you do.
At the dairy I'm only one hundred twenty
point or bad Oh it's awful. And then out
of the crash guy this thing happened last
night. You know and all those reporters
came running up to me I said All
boils royal boy and. I guess I was carried
away when I was getting somewhere.
With the telephone. Going up stairs
hey wait a minute come on I'm
a little on the level I'll give you five
bucks to start the elevator come on let's
get out of case I have a check
get knocked out. When I was
a little boy is not it and you have to go
by God please don't stop me he's nervous
is me what do you suggest. Warming up theory
now he's tried that not if you come on
it's gone. Well when I was
a little boy now that I just are
your lover Oh no I got started on
a little boy I've got no time to wait
for you to grow up oh now I'm on now
you've got em all rattles Now come on
come on intelligence and all of that just
well when I was
a little boy I was sort of puny Hey. You
can get in on this all right thanks the
big boys used to pick on me they threw
things at me bricks and tomatoes you know
like kids do so I'm going to duck
like the duck. See what I mean oh I
had to I finally got to good at it that I
could put my hands in the pockets and.
That the kids pretty easy could knock my
head off they couldn't either you know
what I mean enough to take my mother and
my sister made the pictures think you made
a rash night OK and I'm trying to find
out if I got knocked out and you keep
talking about milk and honey babies I make
now this isn't going to get you anywhere
How'd you like to me do that do you know
why I go it's not where I was. Now let's
say you were a puny little boy and
you took your mother and sister do
a picture show now do you remember oh
yeah. I even remember the picture.
You remember the one where the man locked
the girlies cabin he chased around and
around the last one yes you do yes
how does him my mother took me home
take the witness chair pay attention to
me Don't let your mind wander he put in
a straight line says what he said that going
to stare you got sick you got to think
you're going to touch the snow got us all
nuts around here the first thing you know
you've done to me that you didn't knock him
out I didn't press what I said was that
he said I said I did knock him out of here
that you all hear that it did not come
up high that's all right that's our end of
the door at the Preston not going up no
don't do NOT have no what
are you going to tell
a price he knocked him off it so why.
Your analogy falls you want to put
a left turn around great rock hard again
he can't get away with that I. Think I'm
not going down much of. A cut it I want to
try to do it to settle down what if yes
if you're settled down I'll explain exactly
what happened I go ahead give us the
lowdown well in the first place he swung
at me and missed I NEVER Yes you missed me
then I can hit you and.
No you see what I mean
staff you see Mr Sloan's that's point
number one he swung at me missed so you put
on another man. Hey.
Oh no that's not the way to
do it. Just what I said. But.
Step on this nonsense when you're
kindly tell me how I got knocked.
That just vote that's exactly
what happened why what
a story twice in one day he gave
another demonstration Oh wait
a minute I can explain everything he can
explain better than I can do if it was an
accident why don't actually he's right I
did I'm actually going to give in and say
that not going to be hard on
a topic that only got everybody Perry am
I right that I don't want to do the job
and hope. To God you want to get out
if you find out go get another job.
Say something. OK he'll be all right that
is the shock that's all what he really
need to sleep this is except I'll
give him a spoonful of that in
a glass of water someone should
a lot watching doctor you know brought up
after the time he got his face caught in
the cash register to see the smoke is not
documented your night and I didn't. Come
on I've gone when you're gone it's
nice it's nice. I got it I got
it it was
a duck to say I don't know what gets on my
get out I don't like it I got it it's an
angle and what I got just
a little about your way you have it all
I think about up here I've got it that
really it home.
Oh. Yeah.
But you. How do I know you love me I don't
know you love me. Who.
Gets more. I guess with
a. Plus one. Coming with me
now so I got what to do.
Anyway I'm not going up there again
anyway what's that. Shot give
me that once again I don't
chew my cabbage twice so yes.
A. Two against one man. Yes.
Listen you're looking here I'm going great
is no better baby your daddy won't take
no for
a nest egg thank God no no. No
no not another word how do
you come in with me. God
already gone again.
Come on come on. He's a dangerous
character he's a medical humanity wait
a minute officer did it seems to explain
Yeah I know I'm a witness come on
a way to get out and say well we know.
That guy can find a link but that the
got. A telephone bill how about if we get
a sleeping medicine is a
natural we don't have
a wreck and it could be the biggest like I
just asked for it again and I'm going to
set up starting with you know you got the
idea he knocks over six set up and then I
need you to photograph we have
a new chat the. Spider and I love it we're
all in the spider gotta love it all
right. This is just
a low point it's all my fault for trusting
a love like that I should've had more sense
I should have said something. I want to
go Yeah that's right for life I know it's
not the first nuclear thing you can do
you still in your speech you say to
yourself that's not him thanks for the tip.
This program is coming to use
the courtesy of a mountain
a good guess. You
stop ringing my doorbell
somebody can you have
a week I tell you I got to see your brother
and I tell you my brother isn't here
and I don't believe you believe me when
I tell you I'm going to get sleep. Now.
Oh sorry I didn't know it was yourself
going to be ashamed of yourself
a big fella like you go around wringing
people's doorbells I said I was sorry what
more can I say that's not the idea is the
principle of the thing my wife's been
talking for two hours she finally went to
sleep you come away corrupt. Well what am
I supposed to do about that is supposed
to be before I get so or oh getting tough
just to stop where you are oh wait
a minute buddy my friend this is not going
to Paypal and for two cents I'll let you
have one right OK I'm in business myself.
But I. Just go.
This. Is.
How I spend the I'm in the lobby
where you know oh wonderful
I don't deny that it every time I
think of when I get back. To that.
I'm in jail. The you.
You you you. Have for but you know
that's a misdemeanor to come in
a blank my own mind if you tell me little
boy you are kind of puny that I'm doing.
HEGAN. You know.
What you. Should.
Oh oh oh an old man I use
your telephone yes I need
a doctor I don't know no I'm all
right thank you hello. Hello.
Hello hello hello yes no I How about the
moment just one moment when you hold the
phone I'm talking to someone yes yes what
I want I mean that's what I'm always on
to I'm talking over here you can
find it was I'm talking about
a friend already struck by
how I don't. Hello oh oh
oh. Oh oh oh oh there.
It is tunneling down.
One. Hundred twenty. Five
and I want what I can't hold Oh.
Oh you can use my phone oh three thirteen
third tour thank you thank you very much
you know.
Coming in. The phones of this thank you.
Sure nice of you. Hello how is this
Kenny this Bernie something that Magnus
Yeah she ran in the gutter. Or she won't
get up here our tongues hanging out
a foot thirsty all she could be she had
plenty to drink what she's got to bellyache
here you better get an ambulance this
thirty six last apartment yes. You better
bring a lady appeared so she's not
a lady I didn't think she was
but if you sector does make
a difference what kind of woman she would
act as if she just an old horse so well
thank you very much like to us about
this. No no dog over there oh yes
thank you.
Hello sons are there we maybe you can
help me out one of your men left
a cap in my apartment all about three
o'clock this morning. I don't know its name
well he was about five feet ten
has dark hair and glasses and and
a very pleasant smile Yeah.
Well if you know who it is would you ask
him to stop on the Epi barber shop now
you're
a liar. Too
low well. I was just talking
about you yeah I know.
How that this Oh not very good as up with
a roll night oh this
today yeah I took it to
a good doctor though. No part of their
hopes will be all right you know.
All through. Give me
another shake I'm not sure
yeah.
OK Thank you. You gotta go kind of out.
Give me back my pants you have part of me
Oh don't mind me I work for flying think
it's ten AM Well it's one thing at
a favor from the back what you
think rather than a horse like
a little bell rings say twenty is this
a taste of what I am and you can't do
that no I know what I'm low on so it's
a big. No stopped every night string rain
could lick safer but you don't know what
you've got to fight somebody who studied
it is only out twenty one and I what I
don't like mind I'll never find someone to
tell you I got to make way I gotta fight
somebody pays a good one I
wake. My God say something why
a boy he wants to say something I'm sorry
but I just don't want to fight. That
somebody I'm your friend
I'm honest I applied to be
a fair audio played on man if
you haven't thanked me yes. Get
a picture of this you're up to
here indulge you've got to string
a big caution here the boy and I think the
dames are doing new pups will be in the
street the crowd supporting us are they
going there we go we know you'll walk
because you're the big shot you're fighting
for the title is supposed to abound
eighty thousand people are going to go to
the back I'll answer. There goes the gun
you run like
a tiger he'll eat the tiger ducks that
you're the Tiger he's going to try to duck
again no no but that's nothing like it.
Showing you gotta get that near the. Relax
you're above the nurse come on given you
you had better then. Don't you want to
learn how to duck back in the Polo Grounds
a tiger lead to left or right I
left my ID thousand people attend
a thousand right eighty thousand that's
one field eighty thousand people and not
quite eighty thousand what do you mean by
not quite eighty thousand because I won't
be there to up to him and game talk is
going to this monkey any good but I assure
you I will now I've got here and now I've
got just the right as one on your pay on
our. Why you think you.
Don't like dames that gentleman. Another
doctor for why they don't need to be
trying to make
a fighter out of we want him to when. You
get out of Iraq with the hospitality of
like
a cold shoulder he's the worst no hotel
here the little lady is right my
apologies and my regrets this time.
But yes just one thing before I go if
you think of me at all buddy try to
remember me as I was honest
Sloan Oh I who came to lay
a future in your life
a future that you would be proud of that
your lovely sister would be proud of and
that that that dear sweet faced
kindly old lady would be proud of.
You nobody I sometimes wonder if I have
to man I Mother hope would be. I bet your
mother this week that is what I'm yeah
she would have little trouble to kidneys
lately hasn't she Sis You know Bernie that
some candy if I didn't know I'd swear
that that was my mother maybe it is your
mother was here we moved in maybe that
your father he was here to. Party
that's my horse. How about
a glass of warm milk. I'll
but she was sick Mr Candy I had to take
her to the hospital. Yes I know those
things cost money nobody did I
hear you say you needed cash
a lot oh you couldn't sell our heart I know
Mr King I'm not trying to tell you how
to run your business one time when you care
but I bet you can do that tiredness was
all right for me but she's
worth more that to me
a lot higher No I never had that much money
in the hole like how much yes or no but
I don't get hung up on the right I'll get
into I'm going to have the money I make
you help by signing a contract with
the that will get what a large but
a fortune for a few moments
pleasant employment in
a cool area arena how do I. Good
morning good. Morning
or spider at the ring
oh. My you look lovely this morning
and vice versa Oh thank you.
Oh I don't. Know if you prefer. Oh yeah.
Oh. You perspire easy
don't you know I never mind that way to get
those elastic brother my neck to let's
get going your face fight the bell make you
come out fighting you mix it up in the
middle of the ring it feels so right ducky
trolls are left out suddenly the crowd
goes not there's
a guy down you days than any doubts
eight nine ten and your the wind.
Don't you think that we ought to practice
losing down where you know we're.
House that time.
I keep it on. You know why don't you
fellows was about the same spot
six months later they got the love the
way from them they're all right now.
Have I gotta go on with this you
can't quit Think of your career.
You know it's the monotony the things
getting me down all right let's see where
well oh yes you are the went on you win
and to look good you give me all business
you give now you give me. And
a topic you're given. That was definite
because the bell rings and the other feller
put him out and you EVER for the
right. Now make
a face. Now make
a face this skin like yours I know
there's nobody scare me put him.
Away I'm here to sell you come in swinging
one two boom one two bull stud swinging
Oh no I might hurt you I'll take
a chance I'm very game.
To prove to you two
two two. Two two two. What's holding you
up not again give it all you
got no camera and stand
swinging hard.
Now what's that so I quit.
Tiger Yeah right you too busy I
normally don't get out of then they ask
yes at the sound flower you know what
you know I'm convinced now you hold
a girl like that I tell you
this and then without music.
Drawn on are not the way this and
this is drawn on our full blown
frogs are now not full
blown from the NAACP but.
Oh God not. To run the.
Sun the not. Some NOT NOT
NOT NOT NOT NOT NOT NOT NOT
a lifestyle I'm here Joe will be in to try
to night don't worry about the weight
you'll make it with a quarter million
a chance it's all said spades you come
on the fourth it's not on the night.
Time. Why can't I just put your when I
was in public and get it all what's.
The way you talk speed is the
difference between a smart guy and
a great that all look what's common
our house. Yes I'm coming to make
trouble not get
a hold of me stop them and keep them away
not wanting my house on the stage that's
just just funny tough make a play for
and if she falls for you she'll be
a cinch to handle turn on
a hundred and sixty pounds of
personality and if you want to put in
a good humor and run broke
my leg and how to shoot me.
Hey. Where do you think you are gone
Pauline may know what games in fight is
don't mix that's what we found out.
But I want to say OK Tony. Take him
over and give him
a shower while you're there take one
yourself. Put in your Lose look.
Oh don't worry Paul I'll do the talking
I'll tell that Gabby Sloan Welcome welcome
welcome home and that means the welcome
Miss Pringle Mr McFarlane You know how do
you do I want to talk to Mr Sloan and you
most certainly what up he was there but
he's in town to meet up with good good
maybe I can talk to you now that's
a pleasure if you'll excuse us I'll
be around give it back out and
I'll fix you. All right come
back put back out to me.
I am through with you know don't get the
wrong impression of the fight game just
because
a few fighters walk on the arrows the
Wise Ones don't like me I am why are you
so interested in Burley where. First
place because he's your brother it
doesn't even make sense but I wouldn't
give her a place like this with a cow in
a few chickens and you and me if this thing
works out and it can't miss I'll get
you a place like this and
a million chickens you know I've heard all
that before and I first met you I had
two of everything now
I've got one of nothing.
I will act like a lady than just
a little but I'm about about you
just can't imagine you're being
a spy for. US just to be too nice. And
after money quickly of some sanctions
then I'm going back but then this is
a whole lot of Magnus' don't
you. Like. It came right off
retail I didn't sell you did me
good luck charm. He went for
a lucky one lost your job and you.
Know. I was lucky when I'm accused.
You tell me you think you're also
a nice person. Felons
.
Sorry
longwall
caught it all.
Talking.
A guy hocus terrible. Hope is doing
everything you taught me back off
all old.
Hank. Up right now.
Hearted
. Are
yelling
N L R L.
A
realm
. This so I don't feel too
good. I don't know I think
I got
a chill here this is cover
right here cause. Yeah
I feel better now he's not much to look
at but if you don't think it takes
a lot of discovers what
a champion he not follow He's fighting
it like men total ton and here
are
a. Legend happening.
Just don't. You think I've had enough
boxing lessons this is what you get up to
worry about but everything we taught you
and the good luck course I tell you that
it's if it's.
Less than that with you
now Chas. There isn't
a way Eric in this town I
went through to try an
exit of it Eric
morrow in a couple of people that make
a ten minute are always. Oh wait
I miss you. Thank.
You. So much about ask what you're looking
for I'm looking for I want to say oh my
cooking for right now and I'm going to
find it let's let it ride somewhere where
the want to buy it is just you
know spotted sitting out on.
That side of the house to buy that look
talk to you if you wish to be free if they
get paid when I come back what do you look
at the thing you know no he was cool.
Maybe he's a good luck Johnson
on how. We're going to get like
a military you know Mr Sloan. Has always
run across forty second Street trying to
make
a left hand turn you can. Anyway because
I was running I got to think you got to
wonder if you couldn't put this
fight off tomorrow night maybe
a few more like it some of the boys not be
able to get out again tomorrow I guess.
I quit or Paul No I'm not quitting like
he does but I cannot go No I'm just not
starting I see on a double cross
a guy that never did anything and
he's. You know I. I don't deserve
this spider Tiger Tiger
scares me it's done to me I
hear let me back to you know I'll go down
the fire escape company going to fight on
a jet. Plane. It's now
called the Dog I feel
the show they got
a guy home and thought I would call
the whole thing off oh. By golly.
And don't forget punks despite the
courtesy of wind farms one way to. Put it.
I was raised. With you yes I know we're
going to celebrate it but I'm not going to
fight it all in the first round that is you
said what is not this the fight what do
you mean well it hasn't started
from the supposed to be over.
There the tiger there is coming down the
aisle I try. Not to do that or not but I
can say that. They were going to introduce
Mr McClellan tonight this time I'd
much rather be here with you. Put it mildly
maybe the thought of meeting with the
Taliban again made him
a little bashful. Delp getting all pot. To
talk about things again
and I got. Tied up again.
Television going to get
an update send it in
a ponytail down cold. Air. Tight
.
Enough to. Learn.
Why did you give up on that good ride and
laugh you don't have to fight you know
a lot of men you know but in
a minute if you worry that Harry is
now out of the. Helmet you know I'm
just surprised you because I
get well I guess you. Do it
like how tough this is gonna get it done
is mandatory post I want to say that you
know that all the boys I did I had
a I've never had a boy that's
a dip the step up when I'm alone time.
And with that oh what shall I know.
L.O.L.
It is their own government that
instilling values in you is
a provider. Said
.
To come to. You to.
Islam. It's lone Louis which is known
for his collar was white collar. Stuff you
talked about on the radio that I could
get
a guy's name in the newspapers. For
instance why I mean like who Fritz what
makes
a man stand up in the crowd base and talked
about the Danes got it Bobby Jones has
got it and me and I got it
and they West she got in
a big way I suppose and I had went
on for them to God I'd recommend I
hope to tell you. But I thought. I.
Had to want to come.
F F F.
F F F F
F F.
F. F.
IMO yes.
Yes reduce product. Come on up boys he
was right here is just the ticket and
measure
measure that Aristotle you so I
will tell you what others think
about it and I'm sure thinks. You don't
know ten zero zero zero zero zero zero.
zero Zero zero zero zero zero S.
Well as the total energy in N.L.
And
a waste in just the biggest ideal I've never
thought of in my life to live and leaving
for Chicago tomorrow I'll buy it up letting
them in Scripture and when you think of
it as
a cleansing argument what should
implement any plan N.S.A.
General
thank you.
an N.S.A.
. Meg
a little risk. But I am
thanking. To see Gabby. You should be
the name of heaven here now that's
enough man Cullen honey that's what's going
to tell us one night on the train about
six million ideas of this man has come
up with the beginning about hisself what
a big way and sort of the public
then of a clear sky along comes
a guy. Said Miss Austin Austin not to Miss
Leslie about the defense contracts and
the fifty thousand dollars. I feel like on
the day is on file I see you in my house
and I've invited some friends to get
stuck with the signing of the article is
a big couple. Off unless you touch
her right number one does it
concern. This is the state.
Of the state out of
a picture you killed sure but get ready
when about ice and find everything for you
here's what I had in mind the paper wanted
a full page essay with you in the can't
stand and I guess what I said to them and
it might be better if the two of you
with any Yes sir the idea is to get
a picture of you with the champ line down
all running up time I guess I'm just
going to get. That all right
when I look pretty much up
a little I think my Uncle Podger the
secret that. Fifty thousand will buy
a lot of chicken chicken Tunney it will buy
off yeah minority yes you're right I'm
still trying to find out where the
money is all right here it comes it's
a sunflower dairies insisted that I bet
the fifty thousand back on the chap and I
had to take it. You mean in the speed news
is we have nothing. But how can we lose
I don't know but it'll be in the papers.
So I thought I was like I can't wait to
tell you it's awfully important you see
the night you're going to be the really.
Tough part me. You know what
I'll get married anyway but I.
Always have a little have I
got a lot because you have
a lot on You Tube really barely How about
a picture of you in the love interest Sure
All right Spike Mark was good terrible
stuff on Google that's why don't we do
pretty much with. This. Because well they
all do it at the conduit to God All right
come on let me we've got to get to the
pharmacy and I'll be out of.
Her I.
Met her and. Here.
A small Well I mean what do you think of
me now I think it's all the wrong fight or
. Oh you don't get this and
you're talking to a guy that gets
a little nod job in the think it was
a great fighter I was speed of God I was
thinking I want good punch we can make the
core function minus
a few dollars of the Tigers hospital bills
we gotta pay that what are you willing.
I think to talk too much.
Little money market explain it.
To wait
a minute honey you break big phony baloney
if you don't generalise can you. Taking
a place in the zoo I would stand in the
way of your foul pot committed my brother
you don't understand how I don't know you
don't like public will want to see me
anymore I don't need this it's my only
yote call like it is darling I love you
stand he's breaking up
but it's gone now wait
a minute I promise I want to make hotter
than. I was that. Kind of C'mon let's get
out of it all is back.
City misalign anything that
is. I beg your pardon.
Decision pleasure mission of course. You
do which is why. I'd like to have you
meet some of my best.
Buddy the first part of
this is News agrees with
a part of the second I don't give the Damon
nickel that the part of the first part
agrees with the fighters or else. When you
come away I'm trying to get you some ice
cream to be food with the sweat of the
bodies you do have you're going to affix the
hands unsealed in triplicate now all we
need is the same job as taken to the press
line in Paris give
a lot of us and your right in the middle
son as you all know is an ideal my own
design purely as
a means of raising funds to charity. Because
I know nothing about fisticuffs but
the call is
a witty one makes me very happy when I
think of the thousands of tiny talk to
receive abundant nourishment from this.
Much like to hear the sound flower dairy to
my defense often and human to sound my
sincere expression that ought to kill the
band. Space which is why is there
a contract. You sign on the bottom line the
top lines of credit and you better make
it to Edwards exogamous that. You know
that it would always volatile if this
message I'm not fighting Gary Barlow I
find I want to Janetta stated I was being
watched. You know like blood pressure and
she don't like that none of what I think
I want to. Do sign
a contract I'm not going to fight
right one of them. I got my power
there goes my chicken
calls can he do this.
They're signing the contract like Greg. Are
you going to bring on your latest. Case
. Just the contract. What
seem to be the trouble there's
a contract it's called You know but I don't
want to tell him he wants to know it
still goes I'm not going to fight my brother
in law not your mother well yes say
yes and I don't want to wait
a couple of months as we can't
wait I mean we don't want to be
a patient please take my word for
a couple months is not yet we waited
fifteen years to look at us and we're not
waiting and I'm not fighting
off thanks Pete you've taken
a great load off my mind but I did
you shorted it had me worried for
a night I wasn't sleeping I tried to
milk and everything internally and I. Of
course why am I no longer. Well anyway
night after night I kept seeing the same
dream that was you serious and your three
beautiful kids was Incidently you love
them especially Jr He looks just like you
cut it out with you know well anyway
there they were on the front porch and as
I came through the gate they all started
to scream mama mama there
comes Uncle Bernie the man
a knock out Papa Yeah show that say your
attitude regarding baby simply fascinates
me I miss him Aline I'm
delighted you know you're
a most remarkable fellow you know you're
not so bad yourself. But much as I should
like to sponsor the new found to say and
I find myself deeply affected by what
you've been saying Ray you want to tell me
something about yourself well when I was
a little boy I was conned
a few. Our children will not cry when
they see Uncle they're like No no L.
When you signed that contract Gee
honey you mean you got a contract
a contact I got
a man you know when it gets so low that I
find movement you know I finally got to
get it so I could put my hands in the
pockets and let the kids pennies they could
knock the head off and they could beat it.
But it was that you just did that's the
old box you and that's what's
been reading about the papers.
Nothing like it you know you got to give
up that knee action you're pretty good the
sun like the bullets. Now I'll show you
how I use it yes you swing at me you mean
actually hit just go ahead I will be
there. Oh like that you must let it go
there to stop follow right all right
all right right now I want all right.
You know ready that's
a neat thing you know you're to stand
yes I know where I am you must relax
a home here David. More freedom. And
loosen up you. Don't forget the only I
know that I'm in now now you do it to
me Your Man The No I remember what I thought
you know if you forget is but this.
Very go on the edge of all right.
The
smith all of us hello Dolly how do you do
how do you do we then take this matter up
Nathan who has been. And I
want you now if I don't
again speed says he wants to go through
it was OK when the tide will be there two
minutes but this is just like
committing suicide All right.
Oh there you are. Burly I
don't even know you you don't
know me all Pa you're being facetious
aren't you I was never more serious in my
life the boy I knew went away and never
came back yes you did I'm the same fellow I
could probably show you my driver's license
now you don't understand burly I met
a boy once that well to say the least I
liked him very much oh no no that was the
old really the nice fellow the one who was
kind of course is the humanitarian but
the one who came back came back with the
smell of blood still fresh in his nostrils
Well you're nothing but
a killer you should be hanging on the wall
with the rest of the killers killer. Me
Killer Yes you are you are Dr Jekyll
and Mr Hyde that's what you are
a dual personality and the good side of
your nature is being destroyed by the bad
bits and you Oh that's right. You should
see yourself as I see you when you
get off that train I was never
so mazed in my life it was
a totally different character and that
character is going on and on breaking people
tearing them apart just to satisfy
your lust that you really
can't you just see yourself to her
that she knew the Tiger the killer not
a want any part of
a killer I'm through all power please. Oh
you.
Spider. I can't fight who told you
never mind I'm convinced to do ever
hear if she can hide no other like
a missin A.M.D. Know I
might Marge know I'm
a dual personality no foolin.
I GOT ME YEAH ME But you
know you're trapped I'm
a tramp knows this and
I'm trying to put over
a big deal and this guy's trying to tell
me that Tiger rain fightin was. A couple
of guys got guys
a couple imagining Jacqueline hi They got
talking to him and I don't understand and
I tell you I can understand there's
a curse on the fight around me ransom but
I don't think it's not about what. I buy
and I just get
a little bit so I'm going to fight you
know Mr Sloan on an awful thing oh yeah
let's get
a lair. You see I'm two different people
one is assigned the vote for you can't do
that. But out Mr Strong This is
a very serious matter you see I
have a good side and a bad side
a humanitarian and
a killer and the good muscular bad I've
got to destroy the tiger in me I have to
who gave you that line of Who told
you that Polly Polly Polly. Oh
yes Polly smart girl Polly
she's right there is
a killer you but you you're all confused
it's the killer in you the stalking where
you have battled balled up in the world
are high and low so you are now listen if
you do fight thousands of babies get milk
nothing but the killer in you the bad
side wants to deprive these tiny toddling
touch of their one chance to enjoy life
limb and the pursuit of happiness now imagine
I'm your father why I don't know you
got me there I want to help to kill the
tiger in the country concentrate as you
have never concentrated before Think of
the baby have you got it yes I think of
a bottle of milk that you guys have the
baby's got it did you want me to have it
take away the bottle of milk but you just
give it to the baby would be asking too
much to ask you to take the bottle of milk
you know what you've got left I've got
a baby and he's crying
now he's laughing. So
when
a thousand babies now they're all trying
to help that one troll I was one down the
road crying I think what
a cry for I don't cry from the UK I have
to have it because the killer says no the
killer doesn't want them to have milk the
kid alexy baby starved but the good you
so humanitarian you he loves babies he wants
babies to have no no you're not going
to let that Tiger look I
because you're fighting for
a cause and what the cause through the
baby's champion they're all cheering for.
Three hundred think twenty five
three seventy five four hundred one
a lot of money after those little kiddies
and happen to scan your neck if you don't
know honey and million chickens.
How long oh hello girlie
but he and his noble not yet. Well all
right he says he's been delayed but he'll
make every effort to get the of though
tonight. With the phone to his boss
called about me but it does happen.
You know Doc little Agnes killer just like
your mama. And so not only duck he was
hungry. And she had about
enough that it put away. Just.
To hear you go. Oh I better go there's
a lot of people waiting for me and you
can't go to the I know what you have to do
with Mom you see what the I gotta go but
when the chance show the world I was back
. On no way you can go do you stay there
when mom. Should have always seen you go
by Mama because I just ghosted out the
parked. Oh so if you read the fine well I'm
all mixed up the man that I love is going
to fight my brother whom I love and now
who know at the last minute I've got cold
feet with what to do let it go this far
then pull it's a long story
it's a long story all about
a champion being in disgrace
and a brother needing
a punch in the nose and and you've got to
stop it or why wouldn't worry me Bernie
says be to be all right an hour after the
fight so he did today let me tell you
something and now after the fight they'll
probably find Burley's head in the twenty
first row singing I ain't got no body
always this old what about all those men he
knocked out all parlay Gaddy paid him
to lay down when Bradley couldn't like
anybody and tonight after the
fight say listen how do you have
a single fight Iraqis been very badly
beaten No no I didn't think so well they go
on and they talk like this I don't know
what time it is this is terrible this is
Tell me all this before but I found
a spade I wouldn't Athena like
a dope really does complicate things were
taken care of all speed money aren't you
. Yes it's been my bank why your coat
is Burley's to unburden Drew don't.
Did what he wanted to surprise you he took
all these money and then not himself to
have weighed it in the can he took along
any time I heard you couldn't pay God
he didn't beat that
signal make every effort.
To make you.
God Put come here. To look good.
To hit
a couple with. A. Perfect
. Opportunity. And I am.
I love it I. Am not what I said I'm not.
Trying to get some time for
a crime don't change what's
will do you like doing.
Just hard knocks some you want to but want
to fight crime you know it sounds you
don't sin and they know the soul.
And me thinks wrong yet you
still belong to how I got to do some of
the stuff or time much I was out I got
a ring and take
a few bob sign I got it I got it which no
one misses officials and it means how are
you a little bit of
a funny sounding suss it out
and. The place. The really.
Nice guy. Not only what he's going to do.
But I don't know the know. The real you.
I guess it was close you said yes
we'll get out here we. Have to pull.
The girl there because. It is not
a punishment I don't see all
that well OK. When some.
Even Gentlemen I thank you for your support
in my efforts to supply milk for those
tiny talking. To him.
Oh I. Don't know speech like
yours look like I write
a check get that Oh I do.
Firewalled. Well Donatus. My
goodness. You are here today
we're here to talk to hear they've been
here to talk about us here in the face of
the talk was if you look I shut
that guy last night I was only
a dream you are not expected to want and
I think about it I'm on your side I'm on
your to mortgage on the move
on step up in the. News.
To me instead.
Get ready. For that three
hundred here's the comment I
don't like your stuff but
I'm afraid that if I got
her
early. We gotta make it look
funny if you win with one punch
they'll know it's
a fake I don't know why is guys around
here before and I don't got it I've been
your manager for a long
time you'll save me
a lot of dough if you ever listen to me
listen to me now you gotta make this kind
of puts a crazy. Some out after
a time I always say to. Her
All right. All right.
I had done and this is it anybody doing
this do you know nothing but I don't want
to change it up to the present I got all
right oh I'm not sure I finally found the
thing. I do you put it down you
finally get to know the day. Now how
do you buy time out
Markman
. The same oh.
Oh so very general
thank air.
Are I'm willing to live in
a box again. I said people in the rules
about conduct and I'm not just going to go
to the way I am now I've been to my and
the first to get your take away where one
of you she goes is still.
Getting us out of there.
I'll. Probably really really
don't know and I just can't
find I can't watch
a strange thing is going to knock you out
of the fight we call yes I said I met
your September. Man I. Was right there
at Witness I don't think they were
for another minute or so after this after
my years work I don't think you've met
one to. Try she's right take
a look here you're going to try your
strength on this and your crew who are in
there and you know they.
Are
at
night and I'm going to cut you know
you're going to get your gun wait
a minute. I'm not. Good enough to.
Tell you something for each of
the difference in the. Air.
Area. Area
I am or. A lot.
Of research. There are. There
are early.
Releases.
A litter
a little litter.
A litter.
Airedale not
a litter or.
Air earlier. That
nails.
A lot. I am or.
Murder.
Error.
Learning.
All right.
So your preacher I guess didn't
realize how strong my wife is
a volunteer fire let me alone if I don't
fit for all the pressure I'm going to make
you will if you resign from the ring the
undefeated champion of the world I'll make
you my partner in the daily basis. Oh
that's wonderful Mr author of the world
had the same Evo you make the bunny have
it in you know everybody should be happy
tonight ha now he's alright at
inner city. But like candy in one
pocket he come to some site could you be
can you tell him hands you he can give the
boys up in Adam's Well
anything you say go bomb
a lot of our species
here mate he's fine he's
a wealthy man you see I got all his money
on me again he didn't know the guards
were already.